(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,r,t){"use strict";t.r(r);var s=t(0),a=t.n(s),n=t(3),o=t.n(n),i=(t(9),t(1));function c(){var e=[{questionText:"ASAP Rocky's mother named him after...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Rocky Balboa",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Rocky Marciano",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Rakim from 'Eric.B. & Rakim'",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Randomly",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What city is ASAP Rocky from?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Manhattan",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Harlem",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Queens",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Brooklyn",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What tattoo does ASAP Rocky have across his stomach?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"A$AP LIFE",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"A$AP WORLD",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"LIVE A$AP",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"LOVE A$AP",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What does ASAP stand for?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"As Soon As Possible",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Anything Stands As Peace",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Always Sing About Peace",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Always Strive and Prosper",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"What is ASAP Rocky's zodiac sign?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Scorpio",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Libra",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Gemini",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Taurus",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Aside from being in ASAP, Rocky is also part of...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"AWGE",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"YG",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Cactus Jack Records",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Secret Sound Club",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"ASAP Rocky said if he wasn't a rapper, he would be a/an...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Singer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Photographer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Engineer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Interior Designer",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"What is ASAP Rocky's producer name?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Lord Flacko",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Lord Flvcko",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"RockyTheProducer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"ASAP R",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"ASAP Rocky is featured in which game's soundtrack?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Assassin's Creed: Valhalla",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Cyberpunk 2077",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Call of Duty: Cold War",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Fortnite",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"In Rocky's music video 'Fashion Killa' he co-stars with...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Kendall Jenner",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Chanel Iman",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Iggy Azalea",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Rihanna",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"What was Rocky's debut mixtape called?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Love. Live. A$AP",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Live. Love. A$AP",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"A$AP",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"A$AP Rocky",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What age did Rocky start rapping?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"9",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"13",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"16",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"19",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"In 2004, Rocky served jail time in Rikers Island for drug dealing. He shared a cell with future rapper _____",answerOptions:[{answerText:"ASAP Ferg",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"ASAP Nast",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Casanova",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"ASAP Yams",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Rocky has dated which of these celebrities?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Kendall Jenner",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Chanel Iman",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Iggy Azalea",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"All the above",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Rocky's diet is described as...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Vegan",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Omnivore",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Vegetarian",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Pescetarian",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Rocky has a cousin that is also in ASAP Mob. Who is he?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"ASAP Nast",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"ASAP Ferg",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"ASAP Bari",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"ASAP Yams",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Where is Rocky's father from?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Jamaica",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"America",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Barbados",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Nigeria",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"For his first big tour, he was accompanied by fellow rappers ______",answerOptions:[{answerText:"ASAP Ferg and ASAP Bari",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Drake and Kendrick Lamar",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"SpaceGhostPurrp and ASAP Twelvyy",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Playboi Carti and Lil Uzi Vert",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"In 2015, Rocky played 'Dom' in the movie _____",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Dope",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Zoolander 2",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"All Rise",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Animals",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What is the name of Rocky's debut album?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"HARLEM",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"ASAP Rocky",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"At. Long. Last. ASAP",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Love. Live. ASAP",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"In 2016, Rocky released a clothing line collaboration with...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Dior",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Guess",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Old Navy",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Raf Simons",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"In 2011, Rocky signed his first record deal with...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Sony Music Entertainment",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"RCA",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Epic Records",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Universal Music Group",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"In his teens, Rocky started to sell which drug?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"DMT",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Lean",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"LSD",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Crack",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"What is Rocky's legal middle name?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Athelaston",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Mayers",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Rakim",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Brown",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"In 2015, Rocky's close friend and fellow ASAP Mob member passed away. Which member was it?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"ASAP Illz",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"ASAP Yams",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"ASAP Ferg",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"ASAP Bari",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"In 2013, MTV Video Music Awards Japan gave Rocky the Best Hip-Hop Video award for which music video?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Praise Da Lord",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Angels",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Peso",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Fuckin' Problems",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Rakim is best friends with...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Travis Scott",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Tyler, the Creator",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Kanye West",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"SpaceGhostPurrp",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"In 2019, Rocky was jailed in which foreign country?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Sweden",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"China",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Canada",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"North Korea",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Rocky's signature hair style is...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Corn Rows",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Afro",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"French Braids",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Buzzcut",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Aside from rapping, Rocky is best known for...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Philanthropy",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Acting",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Producing",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Fashion",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Rocky is known to use which drug for inspiration?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"LSD",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Crack",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Lean",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Adderall",isCorrect:!1}]}],r=Object(s.useState)(Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length)),t=Object(i.a)(r,2),n=t[0],o=t[1],c=Object(s.useState)(!1),w=Object(i.a)(c,2),T=w[0],x=w[1],C=Object(s.useState)(0),l=Object(i.a)(C,2),u=l[0],A=l[1],d=Object(s.useState)(0),h=Object(i.a)(d,2),p=h[0],m=h[1],y=Object(s.useState)([n]),k=Object(i.a)(y,2),P=k[0],S=k[1];return a.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},T?a.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"You scored ",u," out of 10",a.a.createElement("button",{id:"reset-quiz",onClick:function(){return A(0),o(Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length)),x(!1),m(0),void S([n])}},"Reset Quiz")):a.a.createElement(a.a.Fragment,null,a.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-section"},a.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-count"},a.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",p+1),"/10"),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},e[n].questionText)),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-section"},e[n].answerOptions.map((function(r){return a.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return function(r){var t;!0===r&&A(u+1);do{t=Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length)}while(P.includes(t));P.push(t),m(p+1),p<9?o(t):x(!0)}(r.isCorrect)}},r.answerText)})))))}o.a.render(a.a.createElement(a.a.StrictMode,null,a.a.createElement(c,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},4:function(e,r,t){e.exports=t(10)},9:function(e,r,t){}},[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.61d77689.chunk.js.map